Spend it with the ones you loathe
A Merry Friggin' Christmas is a comedy film directed by Tristram Shapeero.
Boyd Mitchler and his family must spend Christmas
with his estranged family of misfits.
Upon realizing that he left all his son's gifts at home, he hits the road with his
dad in an attempt to make the 8-hour round trip before sunrise.
Boyd Mitchler, played by Joel McHale.
Luann Mitchler, played by Lauren Graham.
Nelson Mitchler, played by Clark Duke.
Hobo Santa, played by Oliver Platt.
Shauna Welnke, played by Wendi McLendon-Covey.
Dave Welnke, played by Tim Heidecker.
A Merry Friggin' Christmas (Also known as A Merry Christmas Miracle) is a 2014 American
black comedy film directed by Tristram Shapeero and written by Phil Johnston.
The film stars an ensemble cast featuring Joel McHale, Lauren Graham, Clark Duke, Oliver
Platt, Wendi McLendon-Covey, Tim Heidecker, Candice Bergen and Robin Williams.
The film was released by Phase 4 Films on November 7, 2014.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics.
The tone is lighthearted.